<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>PolarClouds</title><subtitle>A minimal, responsive, and powerful Jekyll theme for presenting professional writing.</subtitle> <updated>2022-08-08T17:17:24+01:00</updated> <author> <name>Chris Hall</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2022 Chris Hall </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>PowerShell Credential Handling</title><link href="/posts/powershell-credential-handling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PowerShell Credential Handling" /><published>2022-08-02T01:00:00+01:00</published> <updated>2022-08-08T17:04:51+01:00</updated> <id>/posts/powershell-credential-handling/</id> <content src="/posts/powershell-credential-handling/" /> <author> <name>Chris Hall</name> </author> <summary> One of the things I like to do on this site is to share handy PowerShell scripts. After all PowerShell allows for automation thus making life easier and who wouldn’t want an easy life? Quite often PowerShell scripts need to pass credentials to remote systems/services; for example logging onto an ESXi host or a vCenter server to perform a task or two. How do we handle those credentials? Pre... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>UPS Triggered Shut Down of ESXi from Raspberry Pi - Part 3</title><link href="/posts/esxi-rpi-ups-pt3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="UPS Triggered Shut Down of ESXi from Raspberry Pi - Part 3" /><published>2022-07-23T01:00:00+01:00</published> <updated>2022-08-08T16:57:08+01:00</updated> <id>/posts/esxi-rpi-ups-pt3/</id> <content src="/posts/esxi-rpi-ups-pt3/" /> <author> <name>Chris Hall</name> </author> <summary> Sorry about the tardiness of this post. I had it written, lost it and then found it again… Last time year we looked at our Uninterruptible Power Supply (UPS) hardware setup and the installation of the required software for our solution. If you’ve not seen that post, catch up now. It’s a great read. :wink: As mentioned, this post is part 3 of a multipart series. Find the other parts here: ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>vSphere Compliance with vRealize Operations and Tagging - Part 2</title><link href="/posts/vsphere-compliance-with-vro-pt2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="vSphere Compliance with vRealize Operations and Tagging - Part 2" /><published>2022-07-05T01:00:00+01:00</published> <updated>2022-08-08T17:15:08+01:00</updated> <id>/posts/vsphere-compliance-with-vro-pt2/</id> <content src="/posts/vsphere-compliance-with-vro-pt2/" /> <author> <name>Chris Hall</name> </author> <summary> Last time we looked at regulatory compliance standards and benchmarks, vSphere tag creation and application and finally for the majority of the post at configuring vRealize Operations to continually monitor for system hardening standard / benchmark compliance. If you have not yet seen that post, catch up now. It’s a great read. :wink: As mentioned, this post is part 2 of a multipart series. ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>vSphere Compliance with vRealize Operations and Tagging</title><link href="/posts/vsphere-compliance-with-vro/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="vSphere Compliance with vRealize Operations and Tagging" /><published>2022-06-28T01:00:00+01:00</published> <updated>2022-06-28T01:00:00+01:00</updated> <id>/posts/vsphere-compliance-with-vro/</id> <content src="/posts/vsphere-compliance-with-vro/" /> <author> <name>Chris Hall</name> </author> <summary> In these days of anywhere computing, one of the tools in the arsenal of the good guys is system hardening. But what is system hardening? System hardening is defined as the practice of reducing a system’s vulnerability by reducing its attack surface. Through a reduced attack surface, there is a lower risk of data breaches, unauthorized access, system hacking, or malware infection. Hardening m... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Rubrik Technical Professional</title><link href="/posts/rubrik-technical-professional/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rubrik Technical Professional" /><published>2022-06-22T01:00:00+01:00</published> <updated>2022-06-22T01:00:00+01:00</updated> <id>/posts/rubrik-technical-professional/</id> <content src="/posts/rubrik-technical-professional/" /> <author> <name>Chris Hall</name> </author> <summary> Yup, that’s right, yours truly is now a Rubrik Technical Professional! The Rubrik Technical Professional (RTP) accreditation training prepares technical pre-sales professionals to demonstrate their ability to build innovative data management solutions across Rubrik Rubrik Cloud Data Management (CDM) and Polaris platforms both on-premises and in the cloud. Isn’t Rubrik a backup product? Hist... </summary> </entry> </feed>
